Guide to the Army Specialized Training Division, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Army Specialized Training Program student transcripts, 1943-1945; Accession 2005-A-117
  - Kaye, Arthur Harold (Box 2, Folder 677)
  - Keck, Robert Willis (Box 2, Folder 678)
  - Kellermann Frederick Dale (Box 2, Folder 679)
  - Kelsey, Robert Field (Box 2, Folder 680)
  - Kendall, Frederic Stephen (Box 2, Folder 681)
  - Kenney, John Robert (Box 2, Folder 682)
  - Kenney, Keith Thomas (Box 2, Folder 683)
  - Kepferle, Roy Clark (Box 2, Folder 684)
  - Kerlinger, Frederick Nichols (Box 2, Folder 685)
  - Kerlinsky, Louis (Box 2, Folder 686)
  - Kern, Lawrence Eugene Jr (Box 2, Folder 687)
  - Kessler, Samuel Louis (Box 2, Folder 688)
  - Kiely, Edward Ray (Box 2, Folder 689)
  - Kilian, Robert Charles (Box 2, Folder 690)
  - Kilpatrick Warren Keith (Box 2, Folder 691)
  - Kimmons, William Lauren (Box 2, Folder 692)
  - King, Arthur Alexander (Box 2, Folder 693)
  - King, Jess William (Box 2, Folder 694)
  - King, Paul Clifton Jr (Box 2, Folder 695)
  - King, Peter Francis (Box 2, Folder 696)
  - King, Warren Thomas Jr (Box 2, Folder 697)
  - Kinsley, Robert Thomas (Box 2, Folder 698)
  - Kirkpatrick Robert Larmar (Box 2, Folder 699)
  - Kirsh, Lazarus Alexander (Box 2, Folder 700)
  - Kishbauch, Russel David (Box 3, Folder 701)
  - Kissling, Erwin, Jr (Box 3, Folder 702)
  - Kitchen, Theodore Jckson (Box 3, Folder 703)
  - Klawkoske, August George (Box 3, Folder 704)
  - Klees, Alfred (Box 3, Folder 705)
  - Klein, Joseph (Box 3, Folder 706)
  - Klemke, Henry Edward (Box 3, Folder 707)
  - Kniaz, Julius Leon (Box 3, Folder 708)
  - Koch, William Valentine (Box 3, Folder 709)
  - Koenig, Robert Marvin (Box 3, Folder 710)
  - Koerner, Theodor Cooper (Box 3, Folder 711)
  - Kolb, Paul Edwin (Box 3, Folder 712)
  - Korba, John (Box 3, Folder 713)
  - Kornhauser David Henry (Box 2, Folder 714)
  - Korsakoff, Leonard (Box 3, Folder 715)
  - Kotok, Lester (Box 3, Folder 716)
  - Kovacevich Louis James (Box 3, Folder 717)
  - Kowallzyk, Francis Casmir (Box 3, Folder 718)
  - Kowalsky, Abraham (Box 3, Folder 719)
  - Kraft, Eliot Bernard (Box 3, Folder 720)
  - Kramer, John Vernon (Box 3, Folder 721)
  - Kraut, Alex Saul (Box 3, Folder 722)
  - Krebs, Alfred Herman (Box 3, Folder 723)
  - Krebs, John Randolph (Box 3, Folder 724)
  - Kreugel, Jospeh Eli (Box 3, Folder 725)
  - Kridl, Andrew George (Box 3, Folder 726)
  - Kugler, Fredrick Ruben (Box 3, Folder 727)
  - Kuhn, Harold William (Box 3, Folder 728)
  - Kumataka, Byrd Hajime (Box 3, Folder 729)
  - Kwasha, Owen Bruce (Box 3, Folder 730)
  - Kweskin, Samuel Irving (Box 3, Folder 731)
  - Lacancellera Frank Anthony (Box 3, Folder 732)
  - Laidler, John Cunningham (Box 3, Folder 733)
  - Laird, Ross Donald (Box 3, Folder 734)
  - Lalich, Peter (Box 3, Folder 735)
  - Lamb, Theodore Lafayette (Box 3, Folder 736)
  - Landau, Jean-Claud Charles (Box 3, Folder 737)
  - Lander, John Albert (Box 3, Folder 738)
  - Landes, Jackson Nicholls (Box 3, Folder 739)
  - Landman, Simon (Box 3, Folder 740)
  - Langford, Stephen (Box 3, Folder 741)
  - Lapp, Conrad Jr (Box 3, Folder 742)
  - LaRocque, Marcel John (Box 3, Folder 743)
  - Larson, Bruce Leland (Box 3, Folder 744)
  - LaRue, Robert Frank (Box 3, Folder 745)
  - Laskey, Herbert Martin (Box 3, Folder 746)
  - Latrash, John Fox (Box 3, Folder 747)
  - Lawson, Norman (Box 3, Folder 748)
  - Lawton, Frederick Lawrence Jr (Box 3, Folder 749)
  - Lazofson, Norman Edward (Box 3, Folder 750)
  - Leahy, Frederick Walton (Box 3, Folder 751)
  - Leahy, James Michael (Box 3, Folder 752)
  - LeBar, Frank Michaels (Box 3, Folder 753)
  - LeBlanc, Charles Gerard (Box 3, Folder 754)
  - LeCesne, Archibald Thomas (Box 3, Folder 755)
  - Lee, Richard Jemison (Box 3, Folder 756)
  - Lee, Richard Ming (Box 3, Folder 757)
  - Lee, Robert Storms (Box 3, Folder 758)
  - Lefkovits, Martin Leonard (Box 3, Folder 759)
  - Lefler, Charles Jack (Box 3, Folder 760)
  - Lefstead, Lawrence Irving Jr (Box 3, Folder 761)
  - Lenard, Louis George (Box 3, Folder 762)
  - Lentilhon, Robert Wared (Box 3, Folder 763)
  - Leonard, Robert Charles (Box 3, Folder 764)
  - LePage, Clarence Charles (Box 3, Folder 765)
  - Lerner, Abe (Box 3, Folder 766)
  - Leroux, Roland Valentine (Box 3, Folder 767)
  - Lesnik, Rudolph Joseph (Box 3, Folder 768)
  - Letendre, Donald Henry (Box 3, Folder 769)
  - Lett, Leo Robert (Box 3, Folder 770)
  - Leung, Milton John (Box 3, Folder 771)
  - Levantino, Barney Peter (Box 3, Folder 772)
  - Leven, Stanley (Box 3, Folder 773)
  - Levin, Alan M (Box 3, Folder 774)
  - Levin, Barry Livingston (Box 3, Folder 775)
  - Levin, Harry Leon (Box 3, Folder 776)
  - Levine, Jason Julian (Box 3, Folder 777)
  - Levitan, Harold Selin (Box 3, Folder 778)
  - Levite, Myron (Box 3, Folder 779)
  - Levy, Irwin Herbert (Box 3, Folder 780)
  - Levy, Melvin Gilbert (Box 3, Folder 781)
  - Lichty, James Seldomridg (Box 3, Folder 782)
  - Lincoln, Brayton (Box 3, Folder 783)
  - Lind, Sol Arthur (Box 3, Folder 784)
  - Lindenmayer Bernard Joseph (Box 3, Folder 785)
  - Lioon, Joseph George (Box 3, Folder 786)
  - Liringis, George Ernest (Box 3, Folder 787)
  - Lobel, David Joseph (Box 3, Folder 788)
  - Locke, Edward Ngan (Box 3, Folder 789)
  - Locke, James Harris Jr (Box 3, Folder 790)
  - Lollar, Chester Clark (Box 3, Folder 791)
  - Longdaue, Ernest Francis (Box 3, Folder 792)
  - Lopez, Maris (Box 3, Folder 793)
  - Lopez, Maris Arthur (Box 3, Folder 794)
  - Lopez-Miranda Edward Hubert (Box 3, Folder 795)
  - Louer, Philip Edward (Box 3, Folder 796)
  - Louie, George (Box 3, Folder 797)
  - Lovell, Lloyd Lewis (Box 3, Folder 798)
  - Lowell, Anthony M (Box 3, Folder 799)
  - Lowenhaupt Samuel Brown Jr (Box 3, Folder 800)
  - Lozano, Carlos (Box 3, Folder 801)
  - Luby, Bernard Francis (Box 3, Folder 802)
  - Luce, JOhn Percival (Box 3, Folder 803)
  - Lugt, John Sival (Box 3, Folder 804)
  - Luke, Thad D Jr (Box 3, Folder 805)
  - Lurz, Thomas Albert (Box 3, Folder 806)
  - Lutz, Robert Reese (Box 3, Folder 807)
  - Luz, Manuel Lorenzo (Box 3, Folder 808)
  - Lym, Raymond Sue (Box 3, Folder 809)
  - Lyman, Thomas Amis (Box 3, Folder 810)
  - Macaluso, Joseph John (Box 3, Folder 811)
  - MacAteer, Alan (Box 3, Folder 812)
  - Macbeth, Stanley Alexander (Box 3, Folder 813)
  - MacCollom, George Butterick (Box 3, Folder 814)
  - Mack, Edward Beach (Box 3, Folder 815)
  - Magat, Richard Irwin (Box 3, Folder 816)
  - Magill, Orrin Rankin Jr (Box 3, Folder 817)
  - Magner, George William (Box 3, Folder 818)
  - Magrady, Charles Arthur (Box 3, Folder 819)
  - Mahoney, James Anthony (Box 3, Folder 820)
  - Mahurin, Allen Redfield (Box 3, Folder 821)
  - Maier, Herbert (Box 3, Folder 822)
  - Maillet, John William (Box 3, Folder 823)
  - Maisonpierre Robert Jules (Box 3, Folder 824)
  - Makiesky, Milton Joseph (Box 3, Folder 825)
  - Mamay, Sergius Harry (Box 3, Folder 826)
  - Mancini, Adrian David (Box 3, Folder 827)
  - Mancourt, Frederick VonWitzleb (Box 3, Folder 828)
  - Mandel, Irving (Box 3, Folder 829)
  - Mandeville Andre Alphonse (Box 3, Folder 830)
  - Marble, Floyd Lansing (Box 3, Folder 831)
  - Marcovitch Norman (Box 3, Folder 832)
  - Marks, Alfred Mitchell (Box 3, Folder 833)
  - Marks, Daniel Joseph (Box 3, Folder 834)
  - Marsh, Robert Bryant (Box 3, Folder 835)
  - Marsh, Robert Hilton (Box 3, Folder 836)
  - Martenez, Frank C (Box 3, Folder 837)
  - Martin, Daniel Leroy (Box 3, Folder 838)
  - Martin, Hartley Vincent (Box 3, Folder 839)
  - Martin, John Elmore (Box 3, Folder 840)
  - Martin, Joseph Walter (Box 3, Folder 841)
  - Martin, Sidney Coke (Box 3, Folder 842)
  - Martinez, James McQuillen (Box 3, Folder 843)
  - Martino, Ernest Frank (Box 3, Folder 844)
  - Masnikoff, Leon (Box 3, Folder 845)
  - Mathis, Henry Alfred (Box 3, Folder 846)
  - Matkoff, Louis (Box 3, Folder 847)
  - Matloff, Maurice (Box 3, Folder 848)
  - Matt, Joshua Leonard (Box 3, Folder 849)
  - Matthews, James Myron (Box 3, Folder 850)
  - Mauer, Bernard William (Box 3, Folder 851)
  - Maxwell, Richard Elliott Jr (Box 3, Folder 852)
  - McAllister Roy Grady (Box 3, Folder 853)
  - McAuliffe, Robert Daniel (Box 3, Folder 854)
  - McBryan, Thomas Joseph (Box 3, Folder 855)
  - McCarthy, Eugene Langley (Box 3, Folder 856)
  - McCarthy, James Bernard (Box 3, Folder 857)
  - McConnell, Cecil Loy (Box 3, Folder 858)
  - McCord, King Stewart (Box 3, Folder 859)
  - McCormick, Francis Xavier (Box 3, Folder 860)
  - McDavitt, James Thomas (Box 3, Folder 861)
  - McDonald, Jack Thomas (Box 3, Folder 862)
  - McDonald, Joseph Edward Jr (Box 3, Folder 863)
  - McFall, Andrew Calhoun (Box 3, Folder 864)
  - McGinley, Walter Edward (Box 3, Folder 865)
  - McGraw, Roderick Vern (Box 3, Folder 866)
  - McLaughlin John Francis (Box 3, Folder 867)
  - McLaughlin Ralph Dexter (Box 3, Folder 868)
  - McLendon, Holmes DeWitt Jr (Box 3, Folder 869)
  - McPherren, John Martin (Box 3, Folder 870)
  - McWeeney, Thomas Aquinas (Box 3, Folder 871)
  - McWilliams Jacob Charles (Box 3, Folder 872)
  - Mead, Robert John (Box 3, Folder 873)
  - Medor, Joseph Ralph (Box 3, Folder 874)
  - Meggison, Clifford Lowell (Box 3, Folder 875)
  - Meister, Edward (Box 3, Folder 876)
  - Mendelewitz Manuel (Box 3, Folder 877)
  - Merkado, Fred (Box 3, Folder 878)
  - Merritt, Lawrence Noel (Box 3, Folder 879)
  - Mesney, Peter Michael (Box 3, Folder 880)
  - Midland, Bernt Benjamin (Box 3, Folder 881)
  - Migliaro, Bernard John (Box 3, Folder 882)
  - Mihall, John Joseph (Box 3, Folder 883)
  - Milbert, Seymour (Box 3, Folder 884)
  - Milestone, Joseph (Box 3, Folder 885)
  - Milhendler Bernard (Box 3, Folder 886)
  - Miller, Glenn Amos (Box 3, Folder 887)
  - Miller, Grant Woodrow (Box 3, Folder 888)
  - Miller, Grier Bovey (Box 3, Folder 889)
  - Miller, James Arthur (Box 3, Folder 890)
  - Miller, James Dale (Box 3, Folder 891)
  - Miller, James Everett (Box 3, Folder 892)
  - Miller, Paul Louis (Box 3, Folder 893)
  - Miller, Robert Leonard (Box 3, Folder 894)
  - Miller, William (Box 3, Folder 895)
  - Mills, David Edward (Box 3, Folder 896)
  - Mills, Robert Fletcher (Box 3, Folder 897)
  - Mills, Stanely Ely (Box 3, Folder 898)
  - Minard, Richard Alden (Box 3, Folder 899)
  - Misker, George L (Box 3, Folder 900)
  - Mitchell, Frank William (Box 3, Folder 901)
  - Mitchell, Nicholas (Box 3, Folder 902)
  - Moccia, Anthony Joseph (Box 3, Folder 903)
  - Mole, Joseph William (Box 3, Folder 904)
  - Molloy, Russell Alan (Box 3, Folder 905)
  - Monahan, Sherwood Leroy (Box 3, Folder 906)
  - Mondros, Edward (Box 3, Folder 907)
  - Montminy, Edward Joseph (Box 3, Folder 908)
  - Mooney, James William (Box 3, Folder 909)
  - Moore, John Franklin (Box 3, Folder 910)
  - Moore, Robert Neal (Box 3, Folder 911)
  - Moore, Robert Ronald (Box 3, Folder 912)
  - Moore, Warren Lester (Box 3, Folder 913)
  - Morgan, Earl Wayne (Box 3, Folder 914)
  - Morgan, Robert Farrell (Box 3, Folder 915)
  - Morrison, Douglas Putnam (Box 3, Folder 916)
  - Moskowitz, Samuel Norman (Box 3, Folder 917)
  - Mueller, Richard Frederick (Box 3, Folder 918)
  - Mullane, Eugene Joseph Jr (Box 3, Folder 919)
  - Mulryan, Henry Trist (Box 3, Folder 920)
  - Mundie, William Lade (Box 3, Folder 921)
  - Munro, Donald Newby (Box 3, Folder 922)
  - Murphy, Ancil Hampton (Box 3, Folder 923)
  - Murphy, Arthur Frederick (Box 3, Folder 924)
  - Murphy, Robert John (Box 3, Folder 925)
  - Musci, Alfred Paul (Box 3, Folder 926)
  - Musella, Lawrence Arthur (Box 3, Folder 927)
  - Naegle, Antoine Rowe (Box 3, Folder 928)
  - Naehr, Harry Frederick Jr (Box 3, Folder 929)
  - Nathan, Lawrence Hyman (Box 3, Folder 930)
  - Naughton, Regis Matthew (Box 3, Folder 931)
  - Neef, Charles Franklin Jr (Box 3, Folder 932)
  - Nelson, Henry Manon (Box 3, Folder 933)
  - Nelson, Warren Louis (Box 3, Folder 934)
  - Nelson, Warren Simeon (Box 3, Folder 935)
  - Newman, Paul Sylvan (Box 3, Folder 936)
  - Nicoll, William Alexander (Box 3, Folder 937)
  - Nochlin, Manuel Perry (Box 3, Folder 938)
  - Noone, Frederick James (Box 3, Folder 939)
  - Norquest, Ralph Irwin (Box 3, Folder 940)
  - Norring, Fred Stanley (Box 3, Folder 941)
  - Norte, Daniel Viera (Box 3, Folder 942)
  - Norton, Roscoe Alexander Jr (Box 3, Folder 943)
  - Novack, Harry Samuel (Box 3, Folder 944)
  - Nudelman, Jerome Joseph (Box 3, Folder 945)
  - O'Brien, Frederick Paul (Box 3, Folder 946)
  - O'Connor, James Patrick Jr (Box 3, Folder 947)
  - O'Connor, Raymond Anthony (Box 3, Folder 948)
  - O'Guin, Howard Maurice (Box 3, Folder 949)
  - O'Neal, Major Warren (Box 3, Folder 950)
  - O'Neil, Daniel Charles (Box 3, Folder 951)
  - O'Neill, Francis Arthur (Box 3, Folder 952)
  - O'Reilly, Frank Warren Jr (Box 3, Folder 953)
  - Obletz, Sam (Box 3, Folder 954)
  - Oda, Ben Hatsutara (Box 3, Folder 955)
  - Ogle, John William (Box 3, Folder 956)
  - Ohberg, Gunnar Eric (Box 3, Folder 957)
  - Olson, Gayle William Jr (Box 3, Folder 958)
  - Oost, Stewart Irwin (Box 3, Folder 959)
  - Opiola, Edward John (Box 3, Folder 960)
  - Orgel, Alvin (Box 3, Folder 961)
  - Orlans, Carmi A (Box 3, Folder 962)
  - Osborne, George Raynor (Box 3, Folder 963)
  - Osgood, Freeman Hinckley (Box 3, Folder 964)
  - Ouzts, Julian Wilburn (Box 3, Folder 965)
  - Ozer, Morris (Box 3, Folder 966)
  - Padalino, Vincent Augustine (Box 3, Folder 967)
  - Page, Donald Edwin (Box 3, Folder 968)
  - Palumbo, Jerry Joseph (Box 3, Folder 969)
  - Panning, Clifford William (Box 3, Folder 970)
  - Pappas, Mitchel Nicholas (Box 3, Folder 971)
  - Pappas, Peter (Box 3, Folder 972)
  - Pappas, Peter (Box 3, Folder 973)
  - Parker, Benjamin Franklin (Box 3, Folder 974)
  - Parker, Raymond Avard (Box 3, Folder 975)
  - Parker, William Henry Jr (Box 3, Folder 976)
  - Parker, Walter Woodrow (Box 3, Folder 977)
  - Parry, Charles William (Box 3, Folder 978)
  - Parshall, Ernest Chapin (Box 3, Folder 979)
  - Patterson, Melvin Dean (Box 3, Folder 980)
  - Payne, Conrad Albert (Box 3, Folder 981)
  - Pearl, Sigmund Selig (Box 3, Folder 982)
  - Pepper, Henry Louis (Box 3, Folder 983)
  - Periera, Robert Lewis (Box 3, Folder 984)
  - Perlinski, Thaddeus Henry (Box 3, Folder 985)
  - Perlo, Lionel H (Box 3, Folder 986)
  - Perrin, Eugene Victor (Box 3, Folder 987)
  - Perry, edward Clifton (Box 3, Folder 988)
  - Persson, Maynard Charles (Box 3, Folder 989)
  - Pessin, Lewis (Box 3, Folder 990)
  - Peterkin, John Emory (Box 3, Folder 991)
  - Peters, Daniel Charles (Box 3, Folder 992)
  - Petrone, Raffaele (Box 3, Folder 993)
  - Petrucci, Constant Frank (Box 3, Folder 994)
  - Petrucci, James Frank (Box 3, Folder 995)
  - Pfeffer, Robert (Box 3, Folder 996)
  - Pharr, Leonard Lee (Box 3, Folder 997)
  - Phillips, Everett Cortright (Box 3, Folder 998)
  - Piazza, Anthony Eugene (Box 3, Folder 999)
  - Picciuto, Nicholas Thomas Jr (Box 3, Folder 1000)
  - Pierce, Clarence Del (Box 3, Folder 1001)
  - Pierce, John Burney Jr (Box 3, Folder 1002)
  - Pihl, Donald Greenwood (Box 3, Folder 1003)
  - Pine, Harry Louis (Box 3, Folder 1004)
  - Pinkham, Richard Griffith (Box 3, Folder 1005)
  - Pitsker, Cooper Knight (Box 3, Folder 1006)
  - Plummer, John Frederick (Box 3, Folder 1007)
  - Podbersky, Arthur (Box 3, Folder 1008)
  - Poenisch, Arthur Paul (Box 3, Folder 1009)
  - Poitras, Kenneth Raymond (Box 3, Folder 1010)
  - Polak, Roger John (Box 3, Folder 1011)
  - Polchlopek Vladimir Marion (Box 3, Folder 1012)
  - Polgar, Thomas (Box 3, Folder 1013)
  - Pollack, Arthur Theodore (Box 3, Folder 1014)
  - Pollack, Martin VanBuren (Box 3, Folder 1015)
  - Pollock, Norman Dale (Box 3, Folder 1016)
  - Pon, Alexander Chong (Box 3, Folder 1017)
  - Poniatowski Adam Francis (Box 3, Folder 1018)
  - Porter, Frederick Gerber (Box 3, Folder 1019)
  - Porter, William Ambrose (Box 3, Folder 1020)
  - Portnoy, Murray (Box 3, Folder 1021)
  - Portyrata, Raymond Edwin (Box 3, Folder 1022)
  - Potocki, Richard Edward (Box 3, Folder 1023)
  - Power, Robert Charles (Box 3, Folder 1024)
  - Pratt, James Walter Jr (Box 3, Folder 1025)
  - Pratt, William Brewster (Box 3, Folder 1026)
  - Presberg, Sidney (Box 3, Folder 1027)
  - Pressler, Joseph (Box 3, Folder 1028)
  - Pretzat, Walter (Box 3, Folder 1029)
  - Previti, Leo (Box 3, Folder 1030)
  - Price, James Robert (Box 3, Folder 1031)
  - Prickett, Philip Fayette (Box 3, Folder 1032)
  - Prycer, Charles Andrew (Box 3, Folder 1033)
  - Pucciarelli Donato Dennis (Box 3, Folder 1034)
  - Pugh, Henry Gilbert Jr (Box 3, Folder 1035)
  - Purcell, Andrew Joseph (Box 3, Folder 1036)
  - Pussilano, James Anthony (Box 3, Folder 1037)
  - Putterman, Felix Maurice (Box 3, Folder 1038)
  - Rabineau, Louis (Box 3, Folder 1039)
  - Raczka, Norbert Ernest (Box 3, Folder 1040)
  - Radtke, Robert Ernest (Box 3, Folder 1041)
  - Railsback, George Franklin (Box 3, Folder 1042)
  - Ramirez, Roberto (Box 3, Folder 1043)
  - Ramsay, David Scott (Box 3, Folder 1044)
  - Randall, Harry (Box 3, Folder 1045)
  - Rasch, Rudolf Jr (Box 3, Folder 1046)
  - Ratican, Walter Lee (Box 3, Folder 1047)
  - Raun, Peter Harry Jr (Box 3, Folder 1048)
  - Ravicz, Simon Robert (Box 3, Folder 1049)
  - Rayford, Linwood Lee (Box 3, Folder 1050)
  - Ready, Donald Earl (Box 3, Folder 1051)
  - Ready, Francis Xavier (Box 3, Folder 1052)
  - Ready, John William (Box 3, Folder 1053)
  - Reda, Frank (Box 3, Folder 1054)
  - Redenbaugh Robert Earl (Box 3, Folder 1055)
  - Redmond, John Gailen (Box 3, Folder 1056)
  - Reese, Raymond William (Box 3, Folder 1057)
  - Reeves, Lester Dennison (Box 3, Folder 1058)
  - Reisert, Francis Paul (Box 3, Folder 1059)
  - Remington, Glen Stuart (Box 3, Folder 1060)
  - Rettenmaier Leon Albert (Box 3, Folder 1061)
  - Reynolds, Roy, Jr (Box 3, Folder 1062)
  - Rhodes, Robert Anderson (Box 3, Folder 1063)
  - Rice, William David (Box 3, Folder 1064)
  - Richardson Jacques Gabriel (Box 3, Folder 1065)
  - Richmond, John Frederic (Box 3, Folder 1066)
  - Ridley, Christy (Box 3, Folder 1067)
  - Riechers, Lewis Justus (Box 3, Folder 1068)
  - Beilke, Robert K (Box 4, Folder 1069)
  - Browne, Francis W (Box 4, Folder 1070)
  - Campbell, Walter H (Box 4, Folder 1071)
  - Carlile, Norman A.H. (Box 4, Folder 1072)
  - Dauer, Louis E Jr (Box 4, Folder 1073)
  - Dunn, John (Box 4, Folder 1074)
  - Ghormley, Carl J (Box 4, Folder 1075)
  - Holden, Roubeil A (Box 4, Folder 1076)
  - Horten, Franklin P Jr (Box 4, Folder 1077)
  - Huey, Sam H (Box 4, Folder 1078)
  - Kavanaugh, John J (Box 4, Folder 1079)
  - Lee, Harrison (Box 4, Folder 1080)
  - McCulloch, Raymond C (Box 4, Folder 1081)
  - Mlynarizk, Francis A (Box 4, Folder 1082)
  - Morris, Israel W (Box 4, Folder 1083)
  - Nofziger, Dwight E (Box 4, Folder 1084)
  - Nolte, * (Box 4, Folder 1085)
  - Norris, John M Jr (Box 4, Folder 1086)
  - Riley, Edwin John (Box 4, Folder 1087)
  - Riopel, Albert Lionel Jr (Box 4, Folder 1088)
  - Riskin, Jules Lionel (Box 4, Folder 1089)
  - Ristuccia, Joseph Amadeo (Box 4, Folder 1090)
  - Robbins, Jacob (Box 4, Folder 1091)
  - Roberts, Alexander Simon Jero (Box 4, Folder 1092)
  - Roberts, Thomas Lawrence (Box 4, Folder 1093)
  - Robertson, Donald (Box 4, Folder 1094)
  - Robitaille Francis Joseph (Box 4, Folder 1095)
  - Robitaille Joseph Philip (Box 4, Folder 1096)
  - Robson, Albert Narvin Jr (Box 4, Folder 1097)
  - Rockett, Frederick Charles (Box 4, Folder 1098)
  - Roderick, John Prescott (Box 4, Folder 1099)
  - Rodriguez, Joseph Peter (Box 4, Folder 1100)
  - Rogow, Arnold Austin (Box 4, Folder 1101)
  - Romer, Samuel (Box 4, Folder 1102)
  - Ronen, Seymour (Box 4, Folder 1103)
  - Rose, Harold Joseph (Box 4, Folder 1104)
  - Rosen, Bernerd Seymour (Box 4, Folder 1105)
  - Rosenberg, Alfred (Box 4, Folder 1106)
  - Rosenberg, Norman Maxwell (Box 4, Folder 1107)
  - Rosenfeld, Morris Maynard (Box 4, Folder 1108)
  - Ross, Ernest (Box 4, Folder 1109)
  - Ross, Werner Carl (Box 4, Folder 1110)
  - Rothenberg Daniel Edward (Box 4, Folder 1111)
  - Rothman, Irving (Box 4, Folder 1112)
  - Rotton, William Nelson (Box 4, Folder 1113)
  - Rouda, Frank Harold (Box 4, Folder 1114)
  - Rowell, Robert Herman (Box 4, Folder 1115)
  - Rowles, Leonard Bailey Jr (Box 4, Folder 1116)
  - Rubin, Louis Decimus Jr (Box 4, Folder 1117)
  - Ruddock, Bernard Nathaniel (Box 4, Folder 1118)
  - Ruest, Maurice Francis (Box 4, Folder 1119)
  - Ruppert, Loren Dale (Box 4, Folder 1120)
  - Russell, Reister Edward (Box 4, Folder 1121)
  - Rutenberg, Charles Isaac (Box 4, Folder 1122)
  - Ryan, Bill Shannon (Box 4, Folder 1123)
  - Saal, Hubert Daniel (Box 4, Folder 1124)
  - Sack, Eugene Harold (Box 4, Folder 1125)
  - Sadusky, Milton Robert (Box 4, Folder 1126)
  - Sakwa, Paul (Box 4, Folder 1127)
  - Salisbury, Arthur John (Box 4, Folder 1128)
  - Samuelson, Gordon Axel (Box 4, Folder 1129)
  - Sasson, Edward (Box 4, Folder 1130)
  - Sauer, Frederick Edward (Box 4, Folder 1131)
  - Sawyer, Walter Judd (Box 4, Folder 1132)
  - Scadron, Harvey Matthew (Box 4, Folder 1133)
  - Schaefer, Brenard Jr (Box 4, Folder 1134)
  - Schapiro, Martin (Box 4, Folder 1135)
  - Schaudt, Harry William (Box 4, Folder 1136)
  - Schenck, John William (Box 4, Folder 1137)
  - Scherdlanger Samuel Philip (Box 4, Folder 1138)
  - Schermer, Stanley Oscar (Box 4, Folder 1139)
  - Scherzinger Richard John (Box 4, Folder 1140)
  - Schimke, William Herbert (Box 4, Folder 1141)
  - Schlatter, Bill Eugene (Box 4, Folder 1142)
  - Schlatter, Carl Robert (Box 4, Folder 1143)
  - Schleh, Heydorn James (Box 4, Folder 1144)
  - Schlemeyer William Herbert Jr (Box 4, Folder 1145)
  - Schleske, Edward (Box 4, Folder 1146)
  - Schmoyer, Harvey Lewis Jr (Box 4, Folder 1147)
  - Schneider, Abraham (Box 4, Folder 1148)
  - Schoenberg Earl Melvin (Box 4, Folder 1149)
  - Schoenebaum Carl Frederick (Box 4, Folder 1150)
  - Schoenfeld Charles George (Box 4, Folder 1151)
  - Schoonover Donald John (Box 4, Folder 1152)
  - Schreer, Sidney Pinkey (Box 4, Folder 1153)
  - Schroeder, Lee Edward (Box 4, Folder 1154)
  - Schubert, Frank Anthony Jr (Box 4, Folder 1155)
  - Schuler, Charles William (Box 4, Folder 1156)
  - Schupak, Paul (Box 4, Folder 1157)
  - Schwartz, Joseph (Box 4, Folder 1158)
  - Schwartz, Laskar (Box 4, Folder 1159)
  - Schwartzkopf Charles William (Box 4, Folder 1160)
  - Schwimmer, Seymour Aaron (Box 4, Folder 1161)
  - Scinto, Frank John (Box 4, Folder 1162)
  - Scott, Drayton Trucks (Box 4, Folder 1163)
  - Scott, Raymond Clendenin (Box 4, Folder 1164)
  - Scribner, Robert Ross Irwin (Box 4, Folder 1165)
  - Scudder, Walter Tredwell (Box 4, Folder 1166)
  - Sears, William Robert (Box 4, Folder 1167)
  - Seckman, Mart William (Box 4, Folder 1168)
  - Seidl, William Peter (Box 4, Folder 1169)
  - Seitelman, Max (Box 4, Folder 1170)
  - Selk, Willis Wayne (Box 4, Folder 1171)
  - Serot, Morris (Box 4, Folder 1172)
  - Shackford, Charles Augustus (Box 4, Folder 1173)
  - Shannon, Herbert Brock (Box 4, Folder 1174)
  - Shannon, Robert James (Box 4, Folder 1175)
  - Shapiro, Paul (Box 4, Folder 1176)
  - Sharp, Glen F (Box 4, Folder 1177)
  - Shearman, John Andrew (Box 4, Folder 1178)
  - Sherdell, Samuel Philip (Box 4, Folder 1179)
  - Sherer, William Harrison (Box 4, Folder 1180)
  - Shidler, Atlee Eugene (Box 4, Folder 1181)
  - Shiel, James Francis (Box 4, Folder 1182)
  - Shields, Charles Agard (Box 4, Folder 1183)
  - Shields, Donald William (Box 4, Folder 1184)
  - Shields, Luther Perry (Box 4, Folder 1185)
  - Shifrin, Sanford (Box 4, Folder 1186)
  - Shivers, Frank Remer Jr (Box 4, Folder 1187)
  - Shoesmith, Thomas Paul (Box 4, Folder 1188)
  - Short, William Gale (Box 4, Folder 1189)
  - Shpiece, Harold Edwin (Box 4, Folder 1190)
  - Shreckhise Oliver Eugene (Box 4, Folder 1191)
  - Shreve, Keith Myrle (Box 4, Folder 1192)
  - Siegel, Gerald Peul (Box 4, Folder 1193)
  - Siegel, Reuben (Box 4, Folder 1194)
  - Siegel, Sol (Box 4, Folder 1195)